Eliza M. Danyi

540-250-1611 | eliza.danyi@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I currently work for Henrico County Public Schools as a Systems Administrator building, maintaining, and providing support for systems both in our datacenter and schools across the county. While my job functions vary widely from day to day, my primary skill set is based on Active Directory, System Center Configuration Manager, and VMware. I am comfortable troubleshooting complex issues and providing high-level technical support. I have experience working both independently and collaborating as part of a team and I enjoy learning about and exploring new ideas and technologies.

QUALIFICATIONS AND SKILLS

- Operating systems: Windows, Mac OS X, Linux (RHEL, Ubuntu)
- Networking: Acquainted with network infrastructure, operations, security, and design
- Hardware: Experience with computer system hardware, troubleshooting, and monitoring
- Software: VMware/ESXi, VMware Tanzu, Configuration Manager, Open Manage Essentials, Microsoft Sysinternals Suite, Wireshark,
- Scripting languages: Experience with Powershell, Microsoft Batch Scripting, Bash
- Other: Demonstrated research, analytical, and troubleshooting skills; extensive experience writing and editing written documentation in a variety of contexts

EXPERIENCE

Systems Administrator, Henrico County Public Schools (December 2015 - Present)
Provide Tier-3 support to our on-site technicians and hardware support for Dell servers both in the datacenter

and at school locations. Facilitate image deployment and work with peers to build both Windows 7 and Windows 10 images for our staff and students using a Configuration Manager task sequence. Testing and packaging software for county-wide deployment. Working with Configuration Manager to create reports and provide vital updates and data to management. Developing, documenting, and testing changes for critical systems in a sandbox environment prior to production implementation.

Web Development Intern, S&G Innovation (June 2015 – November 2015)

Developed website features by utilizing skills in JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, and regular expression patterning. Coordinated with the development team to test and integrate new site code. Collaborated with peers and worked closely with the project team to test, debug, and streamline site code.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Information Technology (2015)

Colorado State University, Global Campus

4.0 GPA, Honors Scholar

Relevant coursework: Intro to Computer Based Systems, Introduction to Networks, Information Systems and Security, Intermediate Networking, Object Oriented Programming (Java), Database Management (MS SQL Server), IT Project Management, Network Enterprise Solutions

Undergraduate Coursework, Biology (2007 - 2011) University of Mary Washington